

Ahmet Demiroğlu

</> FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER </>

CONTACT

ahmetdemiroglu.github.io/portfolyo/

□ ahmetdemiroglu89@gmail.com

+90 555 713 70 64

EDUCATION

Neos Yazılım Akademi | 2024

Software Development Education



neos

Department of City and Regional Planning | 2008 - 2013

Gazi University, Bachelor's Degree



Campus Europae Programme | 2010 - 2011

Universidad de Alcalá



İzmir Türk Koleji Science High School | 2003 - 2007

INTERESTS



Travel











Photography



Games

Sports

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am Ahmet Demiroğlu. I am an Urban Planner who successfully completed Gazi University City and Regional Planning Bachelor's Degree and a Real Estate Appraiser with nine years of experiences in field and control stages. Now, I am taking new steps into the software development as a Full-Stack Web Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internship | 2024



Neos Yazılım Akademi

During the internship process that started in April which is a part of the software specialisation education, a fully comprehensive car rental website is being prepared . In addition, I will be participating in the preparation of a native and open source CSS and JS libraries within Neos Yazılım.

Controller | 2017 - 2023



Mülk Kurumsal Gayr. Değ. ve Dan. A.Ş.

I've controlled approximately 9,000 appraisal reports regarding qualified real estate such as Fuel Station, Tourist Facility, Farm, Residence, Land, Field, shopping centre, Industrial Facility etc. within the company where I've worked as a controller.

Appraiser | 2014 - 2017



Form Gayrimenkul Değ. ve Dan. A.Ş.

I've prepared over 1000 real estate appraisal reports for different qualities and controlled more than 1000 appraisal reports which are prepared by real estate appraisers and submitted them for bank approval within the company where I've worked both as a Real Estate Appraiser and a Controller in different periods.

Scholar | 2013 - 2014





Gazi Üniversitesi Tübitak

I took part as a scholar in the TUBITAK project managed by Assoc. Prof. Burcu H. Özüduru at Gazi University and Asst. Prof. Eda Ünlü Yücesoy at Şehir University. I 've done data entry and geocode work in ArcGIS after a quick literature research for the project.

CERTIFICATES, CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

- TDUB Mesleki Tecrübe Belgesi / Sorumlu Değerleme Uzmanı (5 years) Date: 07.10.2019, No: 2019-01.1811
- Neos Yazılım Akademi / Yazılım Uzmanlığı Eğitimi Katılım Sertifikası Tarih: 29.03.2024. No: 00000853
- ICC W Certificate / Software Soecialisation Education Date: 28.03.2024, No: ICCW-2022-30475
- Istanbul Arel Universitesi ARELSEM / Yazılım Uzmanlığı Eğitim Belgesi Tarih: Mart, 2024, UN Kodu: UN_04141400001667704

REFERENCES

Prof. Nihan Özdemir Sönmez

Ankara University Faculty of Applied Sciences - Vice Dean

Tel: 0 (532) 734 82 44 - 0 (312) 363 66 48

Prof. Burcu H. Özüduru

Gazi University, Faculty of Architecture, Department of City and Regional Planning Tel: 0 (533) 225 48 14

Bora Pektezel

Mülk Kurumsal Gayrimenkul Değerleme ve Danışmanlık A.Ş. Responsible Business Partner

Tel: 0 (506) 366 11 00

SKILLS

HTML5	5	****
CSS	3	****
JavaScript	15	****
React		***
JQuery	jauery	
C#		****
ASP.NET Core	asp.net	****
Entity Framework	N	****
SQL Server Management Studio		****
GitHub	0	****
Photoshop	Ps	***

LANGUAGES

ingilizce B2 UPPER INTERMEDIATE ispanyolca A2 ELEMENTARY